
Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry. 
Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s,
 when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type
 specimen book. It has survived not only five centuries, but also the leap into
 electronic typesetting, remaining essentially unchanged. It was popularised in
 the 1960s with the release of Letraset sheets containing Lorem Ipsum passages,
 and more recently with desktop publishing software like Aldus PageMaker 
 including versions of Lorem Ipsum.

It is a long established fact that a reader will be distracted
by the readable content of a page when looking at its layout.
The point of using Lorem Ipsum is that it has a more-or-less normal
distribution of letters, as opposed to using 'Content here, content here', 
making it look like readable English. Many desktop publishing packages and 
web page editors now use Lorem Ipsum as their default model text, and a search 
for 'lorem ipsum' will uncover many web sites still in their infancy. Various 
versions have evolved over the years, sometimes by accident, sometimes on 
purpose (injected humour and the like).
 
Contrary to popular belief, Lorem Ipsum is not simply random text. 
It has roots in a piece of classical Latin literature from 45 BC, making it 
over 2000 years old. Richard McClintock, a Latin professor at Hampden-Sydney 
College in Virginia, looked up one of the more obscure Latin words, consectetur, 
from a Lorem Ipsum passage, and going through the cites of the word in classical 
literature, discovered the undoubtable source. Lorem Ipsum comes from sections 
1.10.32 and 1.10.33 of "de Finibus Bonorum et Malorum" (The Extremes of Good and Evil) 
by Cicero, written in 45 BC. This book is a treatise on the theory of ethics, very 
popular during the Renaissance. The first line of Lorem Ipsum, "Lorem ipsum dolor 
sit amet..", comes from a line in section 1.10.32.

The standard chunk of Lorem Ipsum used since the 1500s is reproduced below for those 
interested. Sections 1.10.32 and 1.10.33 from "de Finibus Bonorum et Malorum" by Cicero 
are also reproduced in their exact original form, accompanied by English versions from the 